## **MOMO MILLER**

P: (810) 599-4690 | E: MINIMOMO14Z@HOTMAIL.COM | BYRON, MI LINKEDIN: HTTPS://WWW.LINKEDIN.COM/IN/MOMO-MILLER|GITHUB: HTTPS://GITHUB.COM/MINIMOMO14

#### **SUMMARY**

After 4 years of working in the financial industry, I'm transitioning from a career as a Relationship Banker to a front-end developer. I have always been interested in learning to code, always wondering how a website or application was made and thinking of ways to improve them.

During my time at Grand Circus Full Stack JavaScript bootcamp, I have gained technical experience in JavaScript, as well as HTML and CSS. Which I recently completed a project where our team developed a memory card game.

I love being able to achieve difficult sections of code to figure out the cleanest solution. because sometimes that kind of code block could take a lot of time to solved and that could possibly effect project from moving forward. As a developer perspective it's completely bringing a huge sense of fulfillment knowing that I've improved both the experience of the user, and other developers working alongside me.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

JavaScript - RACT app - WEB APIs - UI/UX
 Node.js - GitHub/.gitBash - Adobe/photoshop - Express
 TypeScript - CSS - HTML - DOM

## **EDUCATION**

Grand Circus | Full Stack JavaScript Bootcamp

November 2021 – February 2022

Naresuan University | B.A. Business and Hospitality for International Tourism and Hotel Management
Graduated in June 2014

#### PROJECT EXPERIENCE

**Unit One Deliverable** 

Languages used: HTML5, CSS3

- Developed mobile responsive website that showcases use of flexbox, and other CSS properties
- Website showcases removal and implementation of web objects in mobile and desktop version

## LMJ-Matching-Game

Languages used: JavaScript, HTML, CSS

- Collaborated with 2 classmates to construct a memory game implementing CSS animations and JavaScript for pairing and matching
- Utilized VS code debugging for error proofing memory game for optimal performance

# **REACT-ICE-CREAM-WARS**

Languages used: Typescript, HTML, CSS

• Create the "Ice Cream Wars" website as a Single Page Application using React. The site provides ways to support and vote for your favorite ice cream flavor. It is composed of four components: App, Header, AdDesigner, and Votes.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## BANK OF AMERICA – JUNE 2017 – OCTOBER 2021

Relationship Banker/Consumer Credit Collection

June 2018 – October 2021

- Proactively managing risk in every consumer and business services, worked in competitive environment to meet deadlines and seller goals.
- Hands-on, working with retail clients to build and deepen relationships by uncovering financial needs and recommending the best products, services and solutions to meet those needs.

## Client Service Representative (Teller)

June 2017 - June 2018

- Working in fast paced environment managing high-risk transactions, while assisting customers with inquiries and/or problem resolution in a professional and composed manner
- Accurately and effectively processed transactions such as customers deposits, cashing checks, withdraws, making bill payments and purchasing cashier's check.